http://www.winningponies.com/privacy.html

PRIVACY POLICY
WinningPonies, Inc. respects the privacy of our members and the information they provide us, and is committed to protecting member information.
As a part of this commitment, WinningPonies, Inc. agrees to diligently protect information submitted by WinningPonies.com members, including addresses, phone numbers, email addresses and billing information.Your use of the WinningPonies.com site and/or your registration as a WinningPonies.com member constitutes your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the WinningPonies.com site. WinningPonies, Inc. may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. WinningPonies, Inc. will notify customers by post on the site or by email of changes to this policy that will affect information collected from them in the future, and your continued use of the WinningPonies, Inc. site and/or products and services constitutes your agreement to such changes.Your registration account information is password protected for your privacy and security. You may edit this information at any time. However, please use all appropriate measures to protect your password. The protection of each password remains the responsibility of the respective account holder.Information submitted by WinningPonies.com members, including residence address, e-mail, phone number, and the like, are retained and used by WinningPonies, Inc. to protect and administer member accounts, help design and improve WinningPonies.com products and services, diagnose technical problems, and in any other fashion deemed reasonably appropriate by WinningPonies, Inc. to administer the site and improve products and services to members.Sensitive billing information such as credit card numbers and bank account information is not stored internally by WinningPonies, Inc.
Such sensitive member information may be stored by a third-party secure payment gateway which processes billing transactions for WinningPonies, Inc.
This information is only stored if requested by the member, for convenience.WinningPonies, Inc. collects the domain name, IP address, and e-mail address of visitors to its web site, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages on the WinningPonies.com bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with WinningPonies, Inc. via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages WinningPonies.com consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information WinningPonies, Inc. collects is the exclusive property of WinningPonies, Inc. and may be used in any fashion deemed reasonably appropriate by WinningPonies, Inc.Members are advised that in the event of a criminal investigation by state or federal authorities or regulatory inquiry pursuant to WinningPonies, Inc.'s licenses, the member waives any and all rights to account holder information and data in WinningPonies, Inc.'s possession, and member specifically authorizes WinningPonies, Inc. to disclose said data and information to law enforcement authorities and member releases WinningPonies, Inc. of all liability in this regard to the full extent possible by law.For site security purposes, and to ensure the WinningPonies.com service remains available to all members, all network traffic is monitored in order to identify unauthorized use attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage or conduct criminal activity.
Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to this service, are strictly prohibited and shall be punishable under applicable federal law.Members are responsible for informing WinningPonies, Inc. about changes to their personal information.
You can do this by sending us an email or updating your personal account information on the web site.Members can opt-out of future email communication from WinningPonies, Inc. by the following methods:Clicking the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email received from WinningPonies, Inc.Sign in to your WinningPonies.com account, click the ACCOUNT tab, then the Edit Preferences link, where you can update your subscription preferences.Contact us and make a formal request to cease communication.
©2020 WinningPonies, Inc. All rights reserved.  Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy
Home | Blog | RSS | Sitemap
This product was created with data that was supplied by and is proprietary to Equibase Company LLC. All rights reserved. Reuse of this data is expressly prohibited.Data provided or compiled by Equibase Company LLC generally are accurate but errors and omissions occur as a result of incorrect data received from others, mistakes in processing and other causes. WinningPonies and Equibase Company LLC disclaim responsibility for the consequences, if any, of such errors, but would appreciate having any such errors called to their attention.
Horse Betting Tips | Free Handicapping Cost Calculator | Results | Wager Types
Superfecta Betting Tips | Latest News | Horse Racing Tracks | Horse Racing History
